https://www.kriya.org/page/terms-and-privacy/en

Ownership of this website
Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. is the sole and exclusive owner of all rights to (the information on) the website www.kriya.org (the “Website”).
Terms of Use
By visiting, using and/or submitting information to the Website, you accept the terms and conditions of the Terms of Use and Privacy Statement.
You are entitled to access and use the Website for only lawful purposes of personal use. The Website and the Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. trademarks, logos, video materials, pictures and graphics, are proprietary solely to Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. The data and content viewable on and contained in the Website, including, without limitation, all video materials, pictures, photographs, text, graphics, images, icons, line art and other renditions (the “Content”) is copyrighted by Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. It is strictly not allowed to use, copy, download, transmit, compile, publicize, or (re)distribute the Content without the express prior written permission of Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. Using the Website does not entitle you to any ownership or intellectual property rights to the Content. You may not frame or utilize any framing techniques regarding the Website and/or the Content. You may not link to the Website without the express written permission of Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. You may not use any meta tags or any other hidden text utilizing the Website or Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc.'s trademarks, logos or graphics. You are not allowed to transmit, submit or post information on the Website without the explicit prior consent of Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc.
Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. does not make any representations, warranties or guarantees express or implied, regarding the accuracy, correctness, or completeness of the Website and/or the Contents. Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. makes no representation, warranty or guarantee that the Website, including, without limitation, the Content, is free of infection from any viruses, worms, Trojan horses, trap doors, back doors, Easter eggs, time bombs, cancel bots or other code or computer programming routines that contain contaminating or destructive properties or that are intended to damage, detrimentally interfere with, surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any system data or personal information.
Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. does not accept any responsibility or liability, whether in contract, warranty, tort (including negligence) or otherwise, for any damages, including, but not limited to, special, incidental, indirect or consequential damages that include, but are not limited to, damages for any loss of profit, revenue or business, as a direct or indirect result of:
Your breach or violation of the Terms of Use and Privacy Statement;
Your (inability to) access and use of the Website;
Your reliance upon or use of the Content; or
Your downloading of any of the Content.
Use of the Website and the Content is at your sole risk. You shall defend, indemnify and hold harmless Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. and its officers, directors, shareholders, employees, third party contractors, agents, representatives and affiliates from and against all claims and expenses, including, but not limited to, attorneys’ fees arising out of, or attributable to, any breach or violation of the Terms of Use and Privacy Statement by you.
Privacy Statement
Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. does not seek to collect sensitive personal data through this site. If Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. does seek to collect such data, your prior consent hereto will be asked.
Like many other Internet websites, the Website utilizes “cookies” to automatically track and store preferential information about you as you use and navigate the Website. “Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored on your hard drive by your web browser. Cookies track your personal preferences and activities, but in no way contain or refer to any personal information. Non-personal information collected from users by the Website's cookies includes, but is not limited to:
The type of web browser used;
IP addresses;
The type of computer used; and
Home server domain names.
If you do not want cookies to be inserted into your hard drive, you can disable your hard drive’s ability to accept and receive cookies through your web browser. However, keep in mind that if you disable your hard drive’s ability to accept and receive cookies, you may not be able to fully utilize all of the convenience features of the Website.
The Website may contain links to other Internet websites. Such links are not an endorsement by Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. of those websites and/or the companies who own or sponsor them, nor the products and/or services that may be offered there. Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. makes no representations or warranties about, nor is it responsible for, the privacy practices of linked Internet websites.
Disclaimer
The use of the Website is at the user’s own risk. Although Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. attempts to provide accurate and complete information on its site, Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. cannot make any warranties or representations with regard to the information provided on the Website and cannot guarantee confidentiality of any information transmitted on the Website. Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. does not accept any responsibility and/or liability for inaccurate or incomplete information, interference with or corruption of information on the Website, the use, for whatever purpose, of all or part of the information on the Website and/or for any unauthorized access to information on the Website, unless such actions result from gross negligence of Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc.
Miscellaneous
The Terms of Use and Privacy Statement are governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Florida, USA, without regard for principles of conflicts of laws. Any actions or claims resulting from your use of the Website will be brought exclusively before the Courts of Florida, USA. In no event shall you be entitled to punitive, special, indirect or consequential damages, and you hereby waive your respective rights to any punitive, special, indirect or consequential damages, including, but not limited to, damages for any loss of profit, revenue or business.
Kriya Yoga Institute, Inc. reserves the right to amend the Terms of Use and Privacy Statement at any time at its sole discretion and without notice. Your right to access and use the Website is subject only to the most current Terms of Use and Privacy Statement. Changes, revisions or deletions with regard to the Terms of Use and Privacy Statement shall be effective immediately upon their inclusion in, or deletion from, the Terms of Use and Privacy Statement, and the posting of the same on the Website. The effective date of the Terms of Use and Privacy Statement, as stated below, indicates the last time the Terms of Use and Privacy Statement were revised or materially changed. Checking the effective date below allows you to determine whether there have been changes since the last time you reviewed the Terms of Use and Privacy Statement.
Effective date: July 18, 2008
Useful Links
Home
learn.kriya.org
Contact Us
Members Login
Our Blog
Follow Us
KYIO is a non-profit organization. Every contribution is valuable, regardless of how small it is. Donate Now
Copyright © 2020 by Kriya Yoga Institute. All Rights Reserved.    |Terms of Use and Privacy Statement
